Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1927-2010 and undated, bulk 1956-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2011-0080), 1935-2010 and undated, (21 boxes and 1 oversize folder)
  - Writings
    - "13 Memorable Poems" selected by Price
    - Poems, drafts, notes, including a "want ad" for an assistant
    - Yoder: Lion at the Lamb's House draft, (2 folders)
    - Magazine profile of Price, draft with Price's corrections, 2007
    - Lang: The Weather Tower
    - Ardent Spirits typescript, 2007, (4 folders) (Box 21)
    - Untitled portion of a draft
    - Drafts (Box 29)
    - William Blackburn memorial, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Baylor School lecture, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous unsorted bundle of drafts, correspondence, and other texts, (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - A Waiting Beauty (Box 29)
    - A Long and Happy Life, 2008 (Box 29)
    - Writings by Others, (12 folders) (Box 29)
  - Audiovisual
    [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact a reference archivist before coming to use this collection.]
    - Films and digital audiocassettes (Box 31)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity at Duke University, 1954 (Box OS-16)
- Accession 2011-0165, (1 box)
  Audiocassettes featuring recorded readings, interviews, and speaking by Reynolds Price.
  - Audiocassette tapes (Box 1)